<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:id="@+id/main"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".MotivationActivity">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Motivation"
            android:textSize="32sp"
            android:textAlignment="center"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:background="@drawable/shape"
            android:padding="10dp"
            android:textColor="#432"/>

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="300dp"
            android:src="@drawable/motivation"
            android:scaleType="centerCrop"/>

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/recipesText"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Daily Motivation\n\nTake a deep breath and remind yourself how far you’ve come ✨\n\nLife is not about being perfect—it’s about making progress, learning from your mistakes, and continuing to move forward no matter how slow the journey feels.\n\nThere will be days when you feel tired, unmotivated, or unsure of yourself. That’s okay. What matters is that you don’t give up. Even the smallest step forward is still a step in the right direction.\n\nBelieve in your abilities. You are stronger than your fears, greater than your doubts, and capable of achieving more than you can imagine.\n\nChallenges are not there to stop you—they are there to build you. Every obstacle you overcome makes you wiser, tougher, and more prepared for what lies ahead.\n\nStay focused on your goals, but also be patient with yourself. Growth takes time. Success doesn’t happen overnight, but with consistency and determination, it will come.\n\nSurround yourself with positivity, take care of your mind and body, and celebrate even your smallest wins.\n\nKeep pushing, keep believing, and keep showing up for yourself every single day 💪\n\nYour future is bright, and your journey is just beginning."
            android:textSize="16sp"
            android:background="#987"
            android:padding="16dp"/>

    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView>